Winners are skins
Yu и
No.1
Mostopolize
This week averaging 158,inction
Most clicking
Ending
It's Papa!
Christmas Color
What do you think?
I don't know anything.
I just don't know what to expect. I'm not nervous or anything.
I get nervous when I see people.
I'm rarely nervous at gigs.
Isn't that normal for a live show?
It's raining here.
Because we have a Christmas Yoshida-san.
You'll be in the back of the line.
That's great.
Please line up one by one in order.
Please go to the rear platform.
I don't understand.
Okay, from here on out, please line up one by one.
Please line up in order.
Shibuya Haru, Yukaefu, and Ayamatte in front
Potato.
Yes, what? You put chocolate on it?Yeah. What? You dipped it in chocolate?
Yes, it's delicious.
Day one's over, sis.
It doesn't hurt that we'll be playing games for a while.
But with the classes in this venue.
And the concentration I don't usually use
I'm sleepy.
See you tomorrow.
That's not today.
How are you feeling about tomorrow?
I'll do my best.
Bye-bye.
Oh, hey.
You know, just... just go up on the wall, give him a pat on the head.
You want me to do it?
Like this, one step at a time.
Up against the wall, and then pat your head.
Then you put your hand in, and then you lift your head up.
Down.
Somehow.
Somehow, somehow, somehow
Somehow, somehow.
Somehow.
I didn't.
When I tried to make up
The first character I used all the time.
Hollide.Hollaid
Look.
It's in there.
No, it's not.
It's not in there.
Can we talk about this?
Yes, we can.
Let's welcome you, Sim Yamal.
Ukaif.
And Yoshmala.
Welcome, Sim Yamal.
Let's welcome you, Sim Yamal.
Rematch in a bad way
barley
Score one, score one, score one!
One!
Score one!
Please give the batting call to our two winners.
Lisa and Tish, Kiz Yoshida and Frispi.
Hello. This is Frispi.
What is your image of Macau?
What image?
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle.
Ohmido is reincarnational.
First of all, it's great that you took the first step.First of all, it's amazing that you were able to take the first step.
Out of this group...
When I got it, two of them were gone.
I thought I had him down, but he was still pinned.
I didn't notice.
- Liqiu. Lioshan? Lillyfranc? Lillyfranc?
Yes!
Well, have a good day.
Check out the match magicians.
What do you think?
I'm just trying to get in the game.
Not at all. The game's as good as it can be.
I'm getting sleepy.
You've got a lot of energy.
He was running away right in front of me.
When you're in trouble, you just take off.
Yay.
Five minutes, 15 seconds.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Unless you're dying.
Good morning, Deden.
It's 9:00 in the morning, but since we're here in Macau...
Deden.
I'd like to go to Macau Tower today.
But seriously, I just got back to the hotel yesterday.
I went back to the hotel yesterday, and I've been watching the archives of the main streaming and the other Japanese players.
I watched it about 10 times for a couple of hours.
It's nice when you get praised, you know?
Bill Turns was praised.I've been getting a lot of compliments on my work, Bill Turns.
Yeah, that's why I'm in the habit of watching
I'm in the habit of watching myself being praised forever.
Oh.
Deden.
Höher.
I'm going up there.
So I've got my ticket and I'm going to go up now.
One, two, three, four.
You!
Quickly!
Kimi!
This is also a quiet way.
Kuroshi, you can help me with that.
He's walking around with a T-shirt, too.
It's a souvenir.
Let's all wear it together.
Ha-ha-ha!
Separate ones.
Oh, wow.
Is that it?
This is my camera.
Here's my camera.
Aniphone.
I can't trust my life to this.
I can't leave without going around.
Really?
I might come back.Maybe he's coming home.
I'm getting a little nervous.
I'm starting to see things for what they really are.
But I'm hungry.
Come on, let's go.
This feels so good.
Nice breeze.
Nice view.
Was that a window?
Window.
I'll do my best.
Buy, buy, buy.
Oh, hey.
Oh, oh, oh.
That's scary.
Oh, my God.
Wow.
A real walk.
Oh, my God.
This might be the highest walk in the world.
That's for sure.
Ready?
Are we here?
It's okay. It's okay.
Here?
We're here?Did you get here?
Okay. Okay.
Okay. Seat.
Seat.
Okay. Okay.
Here?
This way?
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, look.
Come on. Come on.
Three, two, one.
One more time.
OK, good.
Oh, shit.
How's it going?
It's good.
Are you feeling it?
Yeah, I'm feeling it.
That's a really serious face right there.
Here we go.
Okay. - Okay.
Three, two, one.
Is this it?Is this it?
It's okay.
You okay?
Oh, my God!
It's sour!
Reach out your hand.
Sayonara.
No good-bye.
OK, try it.
Wait!
No!
I don't trust you.
OK, sayonara.
I'd rather fall out.
Really? Really?
Are you sure?
I'll be fine.
You're right... we're gonna die.
What's 321? What's 321? What's the count?
I really don't trust you.
And two. One.
Yes, not even 1
Three. Two.
Three. One.
Yes, that's good.
It's okay. It's okay.
Manji, I'd rather fly.Manji, I'd rather fly.
OK.
Three, two, one.
They're gonna drop us.
Yeah, great.
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Are you okay?
I'm crazy.
Am I crazy?
Bungy's bouncing at the end.
Bungy's bouncing.
See you next time.
Skywalkers are walking.
Fun!
Scary but fun!
Everyone was hilarious
Funny.
Thank you for your hard work.
I have one small regret.
But there are many reasons.
I'll do my best next time.
He's hitting me! He's hitting me!
I'm in the right place, aren't I?I'm right where I want to be.
Mild? Oh, I'm down.
Okay, I'm down, I'm down.
Great timing.
It's okay, it's okay.
What game is "falling"?
Game, game, game, it's falling.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Flamer, stay one more time.
Nice, nice.
Hey, nice.
No, it's Don Mysuke who's down, isn't it?
Nice nice
No, that's right.
Good, good, good, good, good.
Nice, nice.
Oh, nice.
You got three kills.
Yeah. - Really?
Really?
Yeah. - Yeah.
It was a good thing.
There it is. There it is.
Yeah. - Yeah.
But...
I kept getting stopped.
What?
At the end.Last one.
In the apple.
You got in.
Oh, yeah.
That was amazing.
That's all I needed.
That was fun, right?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Yes, that's why I'm here.
The APEX event
is over!
Yay!
The overall result
I was on the team with Mr. Shibuhara again.
I was able to be on the same team with Mr. Shibuhara again
I was able to be with Yuka, a player I've been watching for a long time
It was a great memory for me.
I also enjoyed Macau a little bit.
It was a lot of fun!
Bye bye!